{
  "klass": "Specie",
  "id": 869,
  "dbSymbol": "alcremie",
  "forms": [
    {
      "form": 0,
      "height": 0.3,
      "weight": 0.5,
      "type1": "fairy",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 65,
      "baseAtk": 60,
      "baseDfe": 75,
      "baseSpd": 64,
      "baseAts": 110,
      "baseDfs": 121,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 2,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 1,
      "baseExperience": 173,
      "baseLoyalty": 50,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 100,
      "breedGroups": [
        11,
        6
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 2560,
      "babyDbSymbol": "milcery",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "sweet_veil",
        "sweet_veil",
        "aroma_veil"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869",
        "frontShiny": "0869",
        "back": "0869",
        "backShiny": "0869",
        "footprint": "0869",
        "character": "0869_00",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_00",
        "cry": "0869cry.ogg",
        "hasFemale": true
      },
      "moveSet": [
        {
          "klass": "LevelLearnableMove",
          "move": "aromatic_mist",
          "level": 1
        },
        {
          "klass": "LevelLearnableMove",
          "move": "sweet_kiss",
          "level": 1
        },
        {
          "klass": "LevelLearnableMove",
          "move": "sweet_scent",
          "level": 1
        },
        {
          "klass": "LevelLearnableMove",
          "move": "tackle",
          "level": 1
        },
        {
          "klass": "LevelLearnableMove",
          "move": "draining_kiss",
          "level": 15
        },
        {
          "klass": "LevelLearnableMove",
          "move": "charm",
          "level": 20
        },
        {
          "klass": "LevelLearnableMove",
          "move": "attract",
          "level": 25
        },
        {
          "klass": "LevelLearnableMove",
          "move": "acid_armor",
          "level": 30
        },
        {
          "klass": "LevelLearnableMove",
          "move": "dazzling_gleam",
          "level": 35
        },
        {
          "klass": "LevelLearnableMove",
          "move": "recover",
          "level": 40
        },
        {
          "klass": "LevelLearnableMove",
          "move": "misty_terrain",
          "level": 45
        },
        {
          "klass": "LevelLearnableMove",
          "move": "entrainment",
          "level": 50
        },
        {
          "klass": "EvolutionLearnableMove",
          "move": "decorate"
        },
        {
          "klass": "TechLearnableMove",
          "move": "charm"
        },
        {
          "klass": "TechLearnableMove",
          "move": "fake_tears"
        },
        {
          "klass": "TechLearnableMove",
          "move": "protect"
        },
        {
          "klass": "TechLearnableMove",
          "move": "disarming_voice"
        },
        {
          "klass": "TechLearnableMove",
          "move": "facade"
        },
        {
          "klass": "TechLearnableMove",
          "move": "magical_leaf"
        },
        {
          "klass": "TechLearnableMove",
          "move": "draining_kiss"
        },
        {
          "klass": "TechLearnableMove",
          "move": "stored_power"
        },
        {
          "klass": "TechLearnableMove",
          "move": "fling"
        },
        {
          "klass": "TechLearnableMove",
          "move": "endure"
        },
        {
          "klass": "TechLearnableMove",
          "move": "psyshock"
        },
        {
          "klass": "TechLearnableMove",
          "move": "sleep_talk"
        },
        {
          "klass": "TechLearnableMove",
          "move": "drain_punch"
        },
        {
          "klass": "TechLearnableMove",
          "move": "light_screen"
        },
        {
          "klass": "TechLearnableMove",
          "move": "dazzling_gleam"
        },
        {
          "klass": "TechLearnableMove",
          "move": "metronome"
        },
        {
          "klass": "TechLearnableMove",
          "move": "rest"
        },
        {
          "klass": "TechLearnableMove",
          "move": "imprison"
        },
        {
          "klass": "TechLearnableMove",
          "move": "substitute"
        },
        {
          "klass": "TechLearnableMove",
          "move": "giga_drain"
        },
        {
          "klass": "TechLearnableMove",
          "move": "energy_ball"
        },
        {
          "klass": "TechLearnableMove",
          "move": "psychic"
        },
        {
          "klass": "TechLearnableMove",
          "move": "encore"
        },
        {
          "klass": "TechLearnableMove",
          "move": "play_rough"
        },
        {
          "klass": "TechLearnableMove",
          "move": "calm_mind"
        },
        {
          "klass": "TechLearnableMove",
          "move": "helping_hand"
        },
        {
          "klass": "TechLearnableMove",
          "move": "misty_terrain"
        },
        {
          "klass": "TechLearnableMove",
          "move": "giga_impact"
        },
        {
          "klass": "TechLearnableMove",
          "move": "hyper_beam"
        },
        {
          "klass": "TechLearnableMove",
          "move": "solar_beam"
        },
        {
          "klass": "TechLearnableMove",
          "move": "tera_blast"
        },
        {
          "klass": "TechLearnableMove",
          "move": "misty_explosion"
        },
        {
          "klass": "TechLearnableMove",
          "move": "pain_split"
        },
        {
          "klass": "TechLearnableMove",
          "move": "psych_up"
        },
        {
          "klass": "TechLearnableMove",
          "move": "endeavor"
        },
        {
          "klass": "TechLearnableMove",
          "move": "alluring_voice"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "form": 1,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_01",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_01",
        "frontShiny": "0869_01",
        "back": "0869_01",
        "backShiny": "0869_01",
        "footprint": "0869_01",
        "character": "0869_01",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_01",
        "cry": "0869cry_01.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": [
        {
          "klass": "LevelLearnableMove",
          "move": "aromatic_mist",
          "level": 1
        },
        {
          "klass": "LevelLearnableMove",
          "move": "sweet_kiss",
          "level": 1
        },
        {
          "klass": "LevelLearnableMove",
          "move": "sweet_scent",
          "level": 1
        },
        {
          "klass": "LevelLearnableMove",
          "move": "tackle",
          "level": 1
        },
        {
          "klass": "LevelLearnableMove",
          "move": "draining_kiss",
          "level": 15
        },
        {
          "klass": "LevelLearnableMove",
          "move": "charm",
          "level": 20
        },
        {
          "klass": "LevelLearnableMove",
          "move": "attract",
          "level": 25
        },
        {
          "klass": "LevelLearnableMove",
          "move": "acid_armor",
          "level": 30
        },
        {
          "klass": "LevelLearnableMove",
          "move": "dazzling_gleam",
          "level": 35
        },
        {
          "klass": "LevelLearnableMove",
          "move": "recover",
          "level": 40
        },
        {
          "klass": "LevelLearnableMove",
          "move": "misty_terrain",
          "level": 45
        },
        {
          "klass": "LevelLearnableMove",
          "move": "entrainment",
          "level": 50
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "form": 2,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_02",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_02",
        "frontShiny": "0869_02",
        "back": "0869_02",
        "backShiny": "0869_02",
        "footprint": "0869_02",
        "character": "0869_02",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_02",
        "cry": "0869cry_02.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 3,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_03",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_03",
        "frontShiny": "0869_03",
        "back": "0869_03",
        "backShiny": "0869_03",
        "footprint": "0869_03",
        "character": "0869_03",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_03",
        "cry": "0869cry_03.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 4,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_04",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_04",
        "frontShiny": "0869_04",
        "back": "0869_04",
        "backShiny": "0869_04",
        "footprint": "0869_04",
        "character": "0869_04",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_04",
        "cry": "0869cry_04.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 5,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_05",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_05",
        "frontShiny": "0869_05",
        "back": "0869_05",
        "backShiny": "0869_05",
        "footprint": "0869_05",
        "character": "0869_05",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_05",
        "cry": "0869cry_05.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 6,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_06",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_06",
        "frontShiny": "0869_06",
        "back": "0869_06",
        "backShiny": "0869_06",
        "footprint": "0869_06",
        "character": "0869_06",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_06",
        "cry": "0869cry_06.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 7,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_07",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_07",
        "frontShiny": "0869_07",
        "back": "0869_07",
        "backShiny": "0869_07",
        "footprint": "0869_07",
        "character": "0869_07",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_07",
        "cry": "0869cry_07.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 8,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_08",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_08",
        "frontShiny": "0869_08",
        "back": "0869_08",
        "backShiny": "0869_08",
        "footprint": "0869_08",
        "character": "0869_08",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_08",
        "cry": "0869cry_08.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 9,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_09",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_09",
        "frontShiny": "0869_09",
        "back": "0869_09",
        "backShiny": "0869_09",
        "footprint": "0869_09",
        "character": "0869_09",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_09",
        "cry": "0869cry_09.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 10,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_10",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_10",
        "frontShiny": "0869_10",
        "back": "0869_10",
        "backShiny": "0869_10",
        "footprint": "0869_10",
        "character": "0869_10",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_10",
        "cry": "0869cry_10.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 11,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_11",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_11",
        "frontShiny": "0869_11",
        "back": "0869_11",
        "backShiny": "0869_11",
        "footprint": "0869_11",
        "character": "0869_11",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_11",
        "cry": "0869cry_11.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 12,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_12",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_12",
        "frontShiny": "0869_12",
        "back": "0869_12",
        "backShiny": "0869_12",
        "footprint": "0869_12",
        "character": "0869_12",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_12",
        "cry": "0869cry_12.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 13,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_13",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_13",
        "frontShiny": "0869_13",
        "back": "0869_13",
        "backShiny": "0869_13",
        "footprint": "0869_13",
        "character": "0869_13",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_13",
        "cry": "0869cry_13.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 14,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_14",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_14",
        "frontShiny": "0869_14",
        "back": "0869_14",
        "backShiny": "0869_14",
        "footprint": "0869_14",
        "character": "0869_14",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_14",
        "cry": "0869cry_14.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 15,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_15",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_15",
        "frontShiny": "0869_15",
        "back": "0869_15",
        "backShiny": "0869_15",
        "footprint": "0869_15",
        "character": "0869_15",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_15",
        "cry": "0869cry_15.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 16,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_16",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_16",
        "frontShiny": "0869_16",
        "back": "0869_16",
        "backShiny": "0869_16",
        "footprint": "0869_16",
        "character": "0869_16",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_16",
        "cry": "0869cry_16.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 17,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_17",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_17",
        "frontShiny": "0869_17",
        "back": "0869_17",
        "backShiny": "0869_17",
        "footprint": "0869_17",
        "character": "0869_17",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_17",
        "cry": "0869cry_17.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 18,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_18",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_18",
        "frontShiny": "0869_18",
        "back": "0869_18",
        "backShiny": "0869_18",
        "footprint": "0869_18",
        "character": "0869_18",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_18",
        "cry": "0869cry_18.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 19,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_19",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_19",
        "frontShiny": "0869_19",
        "back": "0869_19",
        "backShiny": "0869_19",
        "footprint": "0869_19",
        "character": "0869_19",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_19",
        "cry": "0869cry_19.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 20,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_20",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_20",
        "frontShiny": "0869_20",
        "back": "0869_20",
        "backShiny": "0869_20",
        "footprint": "0869_20",
        "character": "0869_20",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_20",
        "cry": "0869cry_20.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 21,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_21",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_21",
        "frontShiny": "0869_21",
        "back": "0869_21",
        "backShiny": "0869_21",
        "footprint": "0869_21",
        "character": "0869_21",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_21",
        "cry": "0869cry_21.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 22,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_22",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_22",
        "frontShiny": "0869_22",
        "back": "0869_22",
        "backShiny": "0869_22",
        "footprint": "0869_22",
        "character": "0869_22",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_22",
        "cry": "0869cry_22.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 23,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_23",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_23",
        "frontShiny": "0869_23",
        "back": "0869_23",
        "backShiny": "0869_23",
        "footprint": "0869_23",
        "character": "0869_23",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_23",
        "cry": "0869cry_23.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 24,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_24",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_24",
        "frontShiny": "0869_24",
        "back": "0869_24",
        "backShiny": "0869_24",
        "footprint": "0869_24",
        "character": "0869_24",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_24",
        "cry": "0869cry_24.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 25,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_25",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_25",
        "frontShiny": "0869_25",
        "back": "0869_25",
        "backShiny": "0869_25",
        "footprint": "0869_25",
        "character": "0869_25",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_25",
        "cry": "0869cry_25.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 26,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_26",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_26",
        "frontShiny": "0869_26",
        "back": "0869_26",
        "backShiny": "0869_26",
        "footprint": "0869_26",
        "character": "0869_26",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_26",
        "cry": "0869cry_26.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 27,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_27",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_27",
        "frontShiny": "0869_27",
        "back": "0869_27",
        "backShiny": "0869_27",
        "footprint": "0869_27",
        "character": "0869_27",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_27",
        "cry": "0869cry_27.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 28,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_28",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_28",
        "frontShiny": "0869_28",
        "back": "0869_28",
        "backShiny": "0869_28",
        "footprint": "0869_28",
        "character": "0869_28",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_28",
        "cry": "0869cry_28.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 29,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_29",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_29",
        "frontShiny": "0869_29",
        "back": "0869_29",
        "backShiny": "0869_29",
        "footprint": "0869_29",
        "character": "0869_29",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_29",
        "cry": "0869cry_29.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 30,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_30",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_30",
        "frontShiny": "0869_30",
        "back": "0869_30",
        "backShiny": "0869_30",
        "footprint": "0869_30",
        "character": "0869_30",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_30",
        "cry": "0869cry_30.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 31,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_31",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_31",
        "frontShiny": "0869_31",
        "back": "0869_31",
        "backShiny": "0869_31",
        "footprint": "0869_31",
        "character": "0869_31",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_31",
        "cry": "0869cry_31.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 32,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_32",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_32",
        "frontShiny": "0869_32",
        "back": "0869_32",
        "backShiny": "0869_32",
        "footprint": "0869_32",
        "character": "0869_32",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_32",
        "cry": "0869cry_32.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 33,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_33",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_33",
        "frontShiny": "0869_33",
        "back": "0869_33",
        "backShiny": "0869_33",
        "footprint": "0869_33",
        "character": "0869_33",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_33",
        "cry": "0869cry_33.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 34,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_34",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_34",
        "frontShiny": "0869_34",
        "back": "0869_34",
        "backShiny": "0869_34",
        "footprint": "0869_34",
        "character": "0869_34",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_34",
        "cry": "0869cry_34.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 35,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_35",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_35",
        "frontShiny": "0869_35",
        "back": "0869_35",
        "backShiny": "0869_35",
        "footprint": "0869_35",
        "character": "0869_35",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_35",
        "cry": "0869cry_35.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 36,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_36",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_36",
        "frontShiny": "0869_36",
        "back": "0869_36",
        "backShiny": "0869_36",
        "footprint": "0869_36",
        "character": "0869_36",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_36",
        "cry": "0869cry_36.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 37,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_37",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_37",
        "frontShiny": "0869_37",
        "back": "0869_37",
        "backShiny": "0869_37",
        "footprint": "0869_37",
        "character": "0869_37",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_37",
        "cry": "0869cry_37.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 38,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_38",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_38",
        "frontShiny": "0869_38",
        "back": "0869_38",
        "backShiny": "0869_38",
        "footprint": "0869_38",
        "character": "0869_38",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_38",
        "cry": "0869cry_38.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 39,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_39",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_39",
        "frontShiny": "0869_39",
        "back": "0869_39",
        "backShiny": "0869_39",
        "footprint": "0869_39",
        "character": "0869_39",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_39",
        "cry": "0869cry_39.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 40,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_40",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_40",
        "frontShiny": "0869_40",
        "back": "0869_40",
        "backShiny": "0869_40",
        "footprint": "0869_40",
        "character": "0869_40",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_40",
        "cry": "0869cry_40.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 41,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_41",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_41",
        "frontShiny": "0869_41",
        "back": "0869_41",
        "backShiny": "0869_41",
        "footprint": "0869_41",
        "character": "0869_41",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_41",
        "cry": "0869cry_41.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 42,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_42",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_42",
        "frontShiny": "0869_42",
        "back": "0869_42",
        "backShiny": "0869_42",
        "footprint": "0869_42",
        "character": "0869_42",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_42",
        "cry": "0869cry_42.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 43,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_43",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_43",
        "frontShiny": "0869_43",
        "back": "0869_43",
        "backShiny": "0869_43",
        "footprint": "0869_43",
        "character": "0869_43",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_43",
        "cry": "0869cry_43.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 44,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_44",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_44",
        "frontShiny": "0869_44",
        "back": "0869_44",
        "backShiny": "0869_44",
        "footprint": "0869_44",
        "character": "0869_44",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_44",
        "cry": "0869cry_44.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 45,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_45",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_45",
        "frontShiny": "0869_45",
        "back": "0869_45",
        "backShiny": "0869_45",
        "footprint": "0869_45",
        "character": "0869_45",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_45",
        "cry": "0869cry_45.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 46,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_46",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_46",
        "frontShiny": "0869_46",
        "back": "0869_46",
        "backShiny": "0869_46",
        "footprint": "0869_46",
        "character": "0869_46",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_46",
        "cry": "0869cry_46.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 47,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_47",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_47",
        "frontShiny": "0869_47",
        "back": "0869_47",
        "backShiny": "0869_47",
        "footprint": "0869_47",
        "character": "0869_47",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_47",
        "cry": "0869cry_47.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 48,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_48",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_48",
        "frontShiny": "0869_48",
        "back": "0869_48",
        "backShiny": "0869_48",
        "footprint": "0869_48",
        "character": "0869_48",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_48",
        "cry": "0869cry_48.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 49,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_49",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_49",
        "frontShiny": "0869_49",
        "back": "0869_49",
        "backShiny": "0869_49",
        "footprint": "0869_49",
        "character": "0869_49",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_49",
        "cry": "0869cry_49.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 50,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_50",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_50",
        "frontShiny": "0869_50",
        "back": "0869_50",
        "backShiny": "0869_50",
        "footprint": "0869_50",
        "character": "0869_50",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_50",
        "cry": "0869cry_50.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 51,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_51",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_51",
        "frontShiny": "0869_51",
        "back": "0869_51",
        "backShiny": "0869_51",
        "footprint": "0869_51",
        "character": "0869_51",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_51",
        "cry": "0869cry_51.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 52,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_52",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_52",
        "frontShiny": "0869_52",
        "back": "0869_52",
        "backShiny": "0869_52",
        "footprint": "0869_52",
        "character": "0869_52",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_52",
        "cry": "0869cry_52.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 53,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_53",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_53",
        "frontShiny": "0869_53",
        "back": "0869_53",
        "backShiny": "0869_53",
        "footprint": "0869_53",
        "character": "0869_53",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_53",
        "cry": "0869cry_53.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 54,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_54",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_54",
        "frontShiny": "0869_54",
        "back": "0869_54",
        "backShiny": "0869_54",
        "footprint": "0869_54",
        "character": "0869_54",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_54",
        "cry": "0869cry_54.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 55,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_55",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_55",
        "frontShiny": "0869_55",
        "back": "0869_55",
        "backShiny": "0869_55",
        "footprint": "0869_55",
        "character": "0869_55",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_55",
        "cry": "0869cry_55.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 56,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_56",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_56",
        "frontShiny": "0869_56",
        "back": "0869_56",
        "backShiny": "0869_56",
        "footprint": "0869_56",
        "character": "0869_56",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_56",
        "cry": "0869cry_56.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 57,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_57",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_57",
        "frontShiny": "0869_57",
        "back": "0869_57",
        "backShiny": "0869_57",
        "footprint": "0869_57",
        "character": "0869_57",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_57",
        "cry": "0869cry_57.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 58,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_58",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_58",
        "frontShiny": "0869_58",
        "back": "0869_58",
        "backShiny": "0869_58",
        "footprint": "0869_58",
        "character": "0869_58",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_58",
        "cry": "0869cry_58.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 59,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_59",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_59",
        "frontShiny": "0869_59",
        "back": "0869_59",
        "backShiny": "0869_59",
        "footprint": "0869_59",
        "character": "0869_59",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_59",
        "cry": "0869cry_59.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 60,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_60",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_60",
        "frontShiny": "0869_60",
        "back": "0869_60",
        "backShiny": "0869_60",
        "footprint": "0869_60",
        "character": "0869_60",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_60",
        "cry": "0869cry_60.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 61,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_61",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_61",
        "frontShiny": "0869_61",
        "back": "0869_61",
        "backShiny": "0869_61",
        "footprint": "0869_61",
        "character": "0869_61",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_61",
        "cry": "0869cry_61.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 62,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_62",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_62",
        "frontShiny": "0869_62",
        "back": "0869_62",
        "backShiny": "0869_62",
        "footprint": "0869_62",
        "character": "0869_62",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_62",
        "cry": "0869cry_62.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    },
    {
      "form": 63,
      "height": 0,
      "weight": 0,
      "type1": "__undef__",
      "type2": "__undef__",
      "baseHp": 100,
      "baseAtk": 100,
      "baseDfe": 100,
      "baseSpd": 100,
      "baseAts": 100,
      "baseDfs": 100,
      "evHp": 0,
      "evAtk": 0,
      "evDfe": 0,
      "evSpd": 0,
      "evAts": 0,
      "evDfs": 0,
      "evolutions": [],
      "experienceType": 0,
      "baseExperience": 100,
      "baseLoyalty": 100,
      "catchRate": 100,
      "femaleRate": 50,
      "breedGroups": [
        8,
        8
      ],
      "hatchSteps": 1000,
      "babyDbSymbol": "alcremie",
      "babyForm": 0,
      "itemHeld": [
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        },
        {
          "dbSymbol": "none",
          "chance": 0
        }
      ],
      "abilities": [
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate",
        "intimidate"
      ],
      "frontOffsetY": 0,
      "resources": {
        "icon": "0869_63",
        "iconShiny": "",
        "front": "0869_63",
        "frontShiny": "0869_63",
        "back": "0869_63",
        "backShiny": "0869_63",
        "footprint": "0869_63",
        "character": "0869_63",
        "characterShiny": "0869s_63",
        "cry": "0869cry_63.ogg",
        "hasFemale": false
      },
      "moveSet": []
    }
  ]
}